<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Hms Features</string>




    <!-- Kits Info -->
    <string-array name="account_kit">
        <item>Account</item>
        <item>account_kit</item>
        <item>Signs HUAWEI ID holders into your app without manual login or verification.
            \n Helps you quickly get users authorization to access their information.
            \n Enables your app to automatically input verification codes from SMS messages.</item>
        <item> 1. Quick Sign-in \n 2. Quick QR Sign-in \n 3. Secure Sign-in</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="analytics_kit">
        <item>Analytics</item>
        <item>analytics_kit</item>
        <item>Fully extracting the value out of user behavior and attribute data is key for staying relevant with a constantly changing audience. </item>
        <item> 1. Intelligent dashboards - \n \t\t Monitors app performance in preset and custom dashboards for faster operations.
            \n\n 2. Diverse analytics models - \n \t\t Analyzes events, audiences, funnels, attribution, behavior, retention, real-time data, and app versions for data-driven app lifecycle management.
            \n\n 3. App debugging - \n \t\t Allows final debugging on data reporting, preventing tracing point omission and event attribute setting errors.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="map_kit">
        <item>Map</item>
        <item>map_kit</item>
        <item>Personalizing how your map displays and interacts with your users tailors their experience to them, not the other way around. Make location-based services work better for you so your app works better for your users.. </item>
        <item> 1. Map display - \n \t\t Provides standard maps as well as UI elements such as markers, shapes, and layers for you to customize maps that better meet service scenarios.
            \n\n 2. Map interaction - \n \t\t Enables users to interact with a map in your app through gestures and buttons in different scenarios.
            \n\n 3. Route planning - \n \t\t Supports driving, cycling, walking, and other traveling modes, covering multiple countries and regions around the world.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="push_kit">
        <item>Push</item>
        <item>push_kit</item>
        <item>Your users want relevance and freshness when it comes to content updates. Push instant messages from the cloud to user devices.</item>
        <item> 1. Instant messaging - Gives you a 99% delivery rate even without your app in the background.
            \n 2. Real-time message receipts - Enables real-time receipts sent to your server to help you track message sending.
            \n 3. Targeted pushing -  Precisely pushes messages to target audiences based on tag combinations or topics.
            \n 4. Tailored message styles - Provides common, large image, and custom styles for you to personalize messages and tailor them to your requirements.
            \n 5. Auto language selection - Localizes your multilingual messages to each device for better global operations efficiency.</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="location_kit">
        <item>Location</item>
        <item>location_kit</item>
        <item>Fused Location - Intelligently combines GPS, Wi-Fi, and base stations to give you precise user locations.
            \n Geo Location - Sets up virtual geographic boundaries to detect events such as when a device enters, exits, or lingers.
            \n Activity Identification - Adjusts your app to user walking, running, cycling, driving, or idling.</item>
        <item> 1. Navigation \n 2. Food and Truck \n 3. Travel and Accommodation \n 4. Convenient Living(Local information related to weather) </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ads_kit">
        <item>Ads</item>
        <item>ads_kit</item>
        <item>For high-quality and personalized ads on your app, the Publisher service platform and unique advertising identifiers help you work seamlessly with third-party advertising and tracking platforms while protecting user privacy. Join our open and regulation-compliant ad ecosystem to earn more from your app in a faster and safer way..</item>

        <item> 1. Traffic monetization \n 2. Advertising identifiers \n 3. Partners - AppsFlyer, Adjust, Singular, Kochuva </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ml_kit">
        <item>ML</item>
        <item>ml_kit</item>
        <item>Use a full range of vision and language APIs to build your own AI apps, even if you are not a machine learning expert.</item>
        <item>1. Text - \n \t\t Text recognition, \n \t\t Document recognition, \n \t\t Bank Card recognition, \n \t\t General Card recognition
            \n\n 2. Speech &amp; Language - \n \t\t Translation, \n \t\t Language detection, \n \t\t Automatic speech recognition, \n \t\t Text to speech
            \n\n 3. Vision - \n \t\t Image classification, \n \t\t Object detection and tracking, \n \t\t Landmark recognition, \n \t\t Image segmentation, \n \t\t Product visual search
            \n\n 4. Face &amp; Body - \n \t\t Face detection</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="panorama_kit">
        <item>Panorama Kit</item>
        <item>panorama_kit</item>
        <item>Use a full range of vision and language APIs to build your own AI apps, even if you are not a machine learning expert.</item>
        <item>1. Panorama modes - \n \t\t Provides 360° sphere, partial 360° sphere, and cylindrical/ring views.
            \n\n 2. Display modes - \n \t\t Supports image display in full screen outside your app or on a new layer within your app.
            \n\n 3. File formats - \n \t\t Supports JPG, JPEG, and PNG images.
            \n\n 4. Control options - \n \t\t Allows users to swipe the screen or rotate the phone while adjusting the view.
            \n\n 5. Panoramic video - \n \t\t Supports 360º video display and switchover between panoramic videos and images.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="scan_kit">
        <item>Scan Kit</item>
        <item>scan_kit</item>
        <item>An in-app scanner and generator for 1D and 2D barcodes connects your app to real-world scenarios</item>
        <item>1. 13 mainstream formats - \n \t\t Supports QR Code, Data Matrix, PDF417, Aztec, EAN-8, EAN-13, UPC-A, UPC-E, Codabar, Code 39, Code 93, Code 128, and ITF.
            \n\n 2. Auto zoom - \n \t\t Zooms in to small or distant barcodes.
            \n\n 3. Structured data extraction - \n \t\t Lets your app quickly identify usage scenarios such as connecting to Wi-Fi or adding a calendar event.
            \n\n 4. Enhanced recognition - \n \t\t Detects barcodes despite low visibility, glare, damage, distortion, or blur.
            \n\n 5. Multi-code detection- \n \t\t Processes up to 5 barcodes simultaneously.
            \n\n 6. QR code generation- \n \t\t Converts your input to the best version and error correction level.</item>
    </string-array>



</resources>